(strings playing mid-tempo pop)
♪ The day I first met you ♪
♪ You told me
you never fall in love ♪
♪ But now that I get you ♪
♪ I know fear is
what it really was ♪
♪ Now here we are ♪
♪ So close yet so far ♪
♪ Haven't I passed the test? ♪
♪ When will ♪
♪ You realize ♪
♪ Baby, I'm not like the rest? ♪
♪ Don't wanna break your heart ♪
♪ Wanna give your heart
a break ♪
♪ I know
you're scared it's wrong ♪
♪ Like you might make
a mistake ♪
♪ There's just
one life to live ♪
♪ And there's no time to wait,
to wait ♪
♪ So let me give
your heart a break ♪
♪ Give your heart a break,
let me give your heart a break ♪
♪ Your heart a break ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ On Sunday ♪
♪ You went home alone ♪
♪ There were tears
in your eyes ♪
♪ I called your cell phone ♪
♪ My love,
but you did not reply ♪
♪ The world is ours
if you want it ♪
♪ We can take it
if you just take my hand ♪
♪ There's no turning back now ♪
♪ Baby, try to understand ♪
♪ Don't wanna break your heart ♪
♪ Wanna give your heart
a break ♪
♪ I know
you're scared it's wrong ♪
♪ Like you might make
a mistake ♪
♪ There's just
one life to live ♪
♪ And there's no time to wait,
to wait ♪
♪ So let me give
your heart a break ♪
♪ Give your heart a break,
let me give your heart a break ♪
♪ Your heart a break ♪
♪ There's just so much
you can take ♪
♪ Give your heart a break,
let me give your heart a break ♪
♪ Your heart a break ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ When your lips
are on my lips ♪
♪ And our hearts beat as one ♪
♪ But you slip
out of my fingertips ♪
♪ Every time you run... ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Don't wanna break your heart ♪
♪ Wanna give your heart
a break ♪
♪ I know
you're scared it's wrong ♪
♪ Like you might make
a mistake ♪
♪ There's just
one life to live ♪
♪ And there's no time
to wait, to wait ♪
♪ So let me give
your heart a break ♪
♪ 'Cause you've been
hurt before ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ You try to smile it away ♪
♪ Some things
you can't disguise ♪
♪ Don't wanna break your heart ♪
♪ Baby, I can ease the ache,
the ache ♪
♪ So let me give
your heart a break... ♪
♪ Give your heart a break,
let me give your heart a break ♪
♪ Your heart a break ♪
♪ There's just so much
you can take ♪
♪ Give your heart a break ♪
♪ Let me give your heart
a break ♪
♪ Your heart a break ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ The day I first met you ♪
♪ You told me
you never fall in love. ♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org